Hello friends, welcome back to
our new video.  Then in today's
video I will tell you about this application.  Is
the application a real
app?  Should you take insurance in this
or not?  Ok?  Look,
basically one of these applications
is an insurance application in which you people
insure yourself.  Ok?
As soon as you download the app, you get to
see such an interface inside the app.  Your policy is your
pocket.  You can manage your policy from your own pocket.  You
can take a policy for any member of your family.  Ok
?  First of all, look inside the app, you will
see some such interface.  And you will see some such
interface.  And you will see some such
interface.  And pin and
you can check the complete details here.
Ok?  See what basically happens in this
?  Let me go to the about section and show you.  It is
written here in full detail.
Ok?  You guys can see it here.  Ok
?  Trusted by millions here too.
You can look here very carefully.  Ok
?  See what happens here?
You can get your insurance done here.  You
can insure yourself and your family.  And
yes, you can pay your insurance through this app only.  You
can check the due date.
You can manage everything from a single application.
That too in an easy manner.  Ok?
You guys can see it here.  Ok?  The
app makers have written in complete details what you
can basically do with this app.  Ok
?  Otherwise, if you want to insure yourself then
you can try this application.
That depends on you.  Ok
?  If you need insurance then you can
take it.  Ok?  I will
end this video here.  Rest of this video was on
app review.  Ok?